I got up late yesterday.
I didn’t get up late yesterday.
He went to work by car.
He didn’t go to work by car.
She had eggs for breakfast.
She didn’t have eggs for breakfast.
We did yoga yesterday.
We didn’t do yoga yesterday.
They did their homework last night.
They didn’t do their homework last night.
Did you get up late yesterday?
Yes, I did.
No, I didn’t.
Did he go to work by car yesterday?
Yes, he did.
No, he didn’t.
Did they do their homework last night?
Yes, they did.
No, they didn’t.
What time did you get up?
At eight o’clock.
Where did you go on Saturday?
We went to the beach.
Where did you have lunch?
At school.
What did you do last night?
We had dinner with friends.